<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	
	<string id="st_achievement_1_name">
		<text>Heavy Pockets</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_1_hint">
		<text>Traders may offer you more rare and expensive goods.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_1_descr">
		<text>Although you know what it’s like to be short of cash, you’re not doing too badly at the moment. In fact, sometimes your wealth can be considerable, and traders value a client of your stature.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_1_unlock">
		<text>You have attained the Heavy Pockets achievement.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_achievement_2_name">
		<text>Radiotherapy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_2_hint">
		<text>You have a chance of surviving an emission even without the aid of drugs, provided your health is in order.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_2_descr">
		<text>You managed to survive an emission without taking cover thanks to the anabiotic pills. The effects of this on your psyche are unclear, as you notice a strange silence inside your mind. It seems that you no longer hear a constant stream of thoughts.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_2_unlock">
		<text>You have attained the Radiotherapy achievement.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_achievement_3_name">
		<text>Infopreneur</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_3_hint">
		<text>Traders will now pay you an additional 10% extra for each PDA delivered to them.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_3_descr">
		<text>When you get your hands on a piece of info, you always find the right buyer. Obviously, you always have your own profit in mind when selling information to those who need it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_3_unlock">
		<text>You have attained the Infopreneur achievement.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_achievement_4_name">
		<text>Duga Free</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_4_hint">
		<text>Paths through Yantar and Radar are now accessible to the dismay of Monolith everywhere.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_4_descr">
		<text>After seeing what reckless experimentation has brought to the Zone you have taken action into your own hands. Paths through Yantar and Radar are now open since disabling the Miracle Machine and Brain Scorcher.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_4_unlock">
		<text>You have attained the Duga Free achievement.</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>
