<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	
	<string id="st_achievement_1_name">
		<text>Heavy Pockets</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_1_hint">
		<text>Traders may offer you more rare and expensive goods.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_1_descr">
		<text>Through trading, looting and stealing you have accumulated a small fortune. Your personal wealth is well known and traders will favour your patronage.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_1_unlock">
		<text>You have attained the "Heavy Pockets" achievement.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_achievement_2_name">
		<text>Radiotherapy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_2_hint">
		<text>You have a chance of surviving an emission without anabiotics, but there is no guarantee.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_2_descr">
		<text>Strangely, you no longer feel haunted by the groans of an approaching emission. You believe there to be a chance they may be more forgiving towards you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_2_unlock">
		<text>You have attained the "Radiotherapy" achievement.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_achievement_3_name">
		<text>Infopreneur</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_3_hint">
		<text>Traders will now pay you an additional small bonus for each PDA delivered to them.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_3_descr">
		<text>Whether selling or buying, to many people information is just as valuable as artefacts. Word has spread that you are a reliable source of such a commodity.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_3_unlock">
		<text>You have attained the "Infopreneur" achievement.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_achievement_4_name">
		<text>Duga Free</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_4_hint">
		<text>Paths through Yantar and Radar are now accessible to the dismay of Monolith everywhere.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_4_descr">
		<text>After seeing what reckless experimentation has brought to the Zone you have taken action into your own hands. Paths through Yantar and Radar are now open since disabling the Miracle Machine and Brain Scorcher.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_4_unlock">
		<text>You have attained the "Duga Free" achievement.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_achievement_5_name">
		<text>Well Dressed</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_5_hint">
		<text>There is a small chance of field dressing additional body parts from slain mutants.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_5_descr">
		<text>Rightly so does the Zone's wildlife fear you - as to much of it you were the last thing it saw. Lately, you have noticed your bloody harvest has become exceptionally bountiful.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_5_unlock">
		<text>You have attained the "Well Dressed" achievement.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_achievement_6_name">
		<text>Silver or Lead</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_6_hint">
		<text>Surrendering stalkers may occasionally reveal the location of more than one stash.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_6_descr">
		<text>Bodies and bullet casings litter the tracks behind you. The stories you leave are infamous. You often wonder why some place possessions above their lives. Perhaps things will begin to change.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_6_unlock">
		<text>You have attained the "Silver or Lead" achievement.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_achievement_7_name">
		<text>Mechanized Warfare</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_7_hint">
		<text>You are able to fully upgrade equipment at a technician other than just the Forester.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_7_descr">
		<text>Basic tools? Check. Advanced tools? Check. Expert tools? Check! That mechanic should prove useful should I need my equipment upgraded. Some extra armour and a grenade launcher wouldn't go amiss.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_achievement_7_unlock">
		<text>You have attained the "Mechanized Warfare" achievement.</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>
