<string_table>

	<!-- The texts in this file are used by the official weapon pack addons. -->
	
    <string id="st_wpn_aps_name">
        <text>Stechkin APS</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_aps_descr">
        <text>The Stechkin APS is a Soviet selective fire machine pistol. It bears the name of its developer, Igor Stechkin.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_beretta_name">
        <text>Beretta 92</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_beretta_descr_alt">
        <text>The Beretta 92 is a series of semi-automatic pistols designed and manufactured by Beretta of Italy. The model 92 was designed in 1972 and production of many variants in different calibres continues today.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_colt1911_name">
        <text>Colt M1911</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_colt1911_descr_alt">
        <text>The M1911 is a single-action, semi-automatic, magazine-fed, recoil-operated pistol chambered for the .45 ACP cartridge. It served as the standard-issue side-arm for the United States Armed Forces from 1911 to 1986.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_colt_kimber_name">
        <text>Kimber Warrior</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_colt_kimber_descr">
        <text>The Kimber Warrior is an M1911 style semi-automatic pistol based on a special version of the Kimber Custom. The pistol has a matte black KimPro finish and a standard Kimber Custom trigger</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_cz75_name">
        <text>CZ 75</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_cz75_auto_name">
        <text>CZ 75 Automatic</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_cz75_descr">
        <text>The CZ 75 is Czech pistol first introduced in 1975, it is one of the original "wonder nines" featuring a staggered-column magazine, all-steel construction, and a hammer forged barrel.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_desert_eagle_name">
        <text>IMI Desert Eagle</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_desert_eagle_descr">
        <text>The IMI Desert Eagle is a semi-automatic handgun notable for chambering the largest centerfire cartridge of any magazine fed, self-loading pistol. It has a unique design with a triangular barrel and large muzzle. </text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_desert_eagle_nimble_name">
        <text>"Steppe Eagle"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_desert_eagle_nimble_descr_alt">
        <text>The "Steppe Eagle" is a modified IMI Desert Eagle sold by Nimble. It boasts slightly increased accuracy over the standard model.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_gsh18_name">
        <text>GSh-18</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_gsh18_descr">
        <text>The GSh-18 is a 9mm semi-automatic pistol developed by the KBP Instrument Design Bureau in Tula during the 1990s. The pistol's name is derived from its designers - Gryazev and Shipunov, and the number 18 denotes the magazine capacity.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_fn57_name">
        <text>FN Five-seven</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fn57_descr">
        <text>The FN Five-seven is a semi-automatic pistol designed and manufactured by FN Herstal in Belgium. The pistol was developed in conjunction with the FN P90 and the FN 5.7x28mm cartridge.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_glock_name">
        <text>Glock 17</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_glock_descr">
        <text>The Glock pistol is a series of polymer-framed, short recoil-operated, locked-breech semi-automatic pistols designed and produced by Glock GmbH, located in Deutsch-Wagram, Austria.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_fort_name">
        <text>Fort-12</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fort_descr_alt">
        <text>The Fort-12 is a semi-automatic pistol which was designed in the late 1990s by Ukrainian firearms designer RPC Fort.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_fort_snag_name">
        <text>Fort-17</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fort_snag_descr">
        <text>The Fort-17 is a semi-automatic pistol which was designed in the late 1990s by Ukrainian firearms designer RPC Fort. This variant of the pistol has a magazine capacity of 17 rounds.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_fnp45_name">
        <text>FN FNP-45</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fnp45_descr">
        <text>The FN FNP pistol is a series of semi-automatic, polymer-framed pistols manufactured in Columbia by FN Herstal America.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_fnx45_name">
        <text>"Autumn Wind"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fnx45_descr">
        <text>The "Autumn Wind" is a modified FN FNX-45 sold by Nimble. It boasts a permanently attached DOCTER sight and suppressor.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_hpsa_name">
        <text>Browning Hi-Power</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_hpsa_descr_alt">
        <text>The Browning Hi-Power is a single-action, semi-automatic handgun based on a design by American firearms inventor John Browning, and completed by Dieudonne Saive of FN Herstal.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_mp443_name">
        <text>MP-443 Grach</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_mp443_descr">
        <text>The MP-443 Grach is the Russian pistol developed in response to Russian military trials. It was adopted as a standard sidearm for all branches of Russian military and law enforcement.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_oc33_name">
        <text>OTs-33 Pernach</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_oc33_descr">
        <text>The OTs-33 Pernach is an automatic pistol designed to replace the Stechkin APS in various special OMON units within the Russian police, the Russian Ministry of Internal Affairs and other paramilitary units.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_pb_name">
        <text>PB</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_pb_descr_alt">
        <text>The PB is a Soviet suppressed pistol, based on the Makarov pistol design. It was issued into service in 1967. The pistol may also be fired safely without the additional suppressor attachment, which may be important in critical situations.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_pm_name">
        <text>Makarov PM</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_pm_descr_alt">
        <text>The Makarov PM is a Russian semi-automatic pistol. Under the project leadership of Nikolay Fyodorovich Makarov, it became the Soviet Union's standard military and police side arm from 1951 to 1991.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_pm_actor_name">
        <text>Ceremonial Makarov PM</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_pm_actor_descr_alt">
        <text>A ceremonial Makarov PM once awarded to Major Degtyarev, as the engraving on the side would suggest. How it ended up in the Zone or how it fell out of his possession is unclear.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_pmm_name">
        <text>Makarov PMM</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_pmm_descr">
        <text>The Makarov PMM is modernised version of the standard PM pistol developed during 1990. The PMM magazine holds 12 rounds, compared to the standard PM's eight.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_sig220_name">
        <text>SIG Sauer P220</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_sig220_descr_alt">
        <text>The P220 is a semi-automatic pistol made by SIG Sauer. The pistol was developed in 1975 for the Swiss Army as a replacement for the SIG P210.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_tt33_name">
        <text>Tokarev TT-33</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_tt33_descr">
        <text>The TT-33 is a Russian semi-automatic pistol. It is essentially a redesigned TT-30 but much simpler to manufacture, which itself was originally developed in the early 1930s to replace the ageing Nagant M1895 revolver.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_usp_name">
        <text>H&amp;K USP .45</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_usp_descr_alt">
        <text>The USP is a semi-automatic pistol developed by Heckler &amp; Koch GmbH as a replacement for the P7 series of handguns. One of the most significant features of the USP is the mechanical recoil reduction system.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_usp_nimble_name">
        <text>H&amp;K USP Match</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_usp_nimble_descr_alt">
        <text>The USP Match is specifically designed to appeal to target shooters. The Match distinguishes itself by its barrel weight, which provides counterbalance to the weapon's recoil, greatly improving follow up target tracking.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_walther_name">
        <text>Walther P99</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_walther_descr_alt">
        <text>The Walther P99 is a semi-automatic pistol developed for law enforcement, security forces and the civilian shooting market as a replacement for the Walther P5 and the P88.</text>
    </string>
	
</string_table>