<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
   <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_0">
        <text>I want to fight. Whom do you have this time?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_1">
        <text>Now there is noone to fight with. Come again later when we have a new batch of mutants from Duty.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_100">
        <text>Now you have to give money for participation. 1000 roubles.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_101">
        <text>Here your 1000 roubles</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_105">
        <text>I don't have any money.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_1051">
        <text>Darn it, another beggar here.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_110">
        <text>You owe me 2000 roubles for the participation.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_111">
        <text>Here's 2000 roubles.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_115">
        <text>I have no money.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_1151">
        <text>And where do these tramps come from in the Zone?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_120">
        <text>Pay 3000 roubles for participation and the bloodsucker is ready.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_121">
        <text>Here's your money.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_125">
        <text>I don't have such a sum.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_1251">
        <text>Damn, even my little son has such money.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_130">
        <text>Not so fast. First pay 5000 roubles for the participation.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_131">
        <text>Here's the money.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_135">
        <text>I have no money.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_1351">
        <text>Don't try pretending a beggar.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_140">
        <text>If agree, then pay 5000 for participation.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_141">
        <text>Here, your 5000 roubles.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_145">
        <text>I don't have money.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_1451">
        <text>Even stalkers can be tramps too. I can't recognize this world.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_2">
        <text>There's a pseudodog. A large specie, but quite beaten up. On the other hand, a very fierce one, same as my mother-in-law. I'm blessed to have never seen her.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_200">
        <text>Deal. One more thing. Put the stake on time you kill the monster within. If you do it - you win, otherwise - you lose. The less the time chosen, the bigger is the money won.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_201">
        <text>30 seconds, tripple win.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_202">
        <text>One and a half minute, double win.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_203">
        <text>Without time limit. A half-stake win.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_204">
        <text>I changed my mind.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_2041">
        <text>Pooh, milksop. I will not return your money anyway.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_21">
        <text>I will try. Let your dog out.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_22">
        <text>No, I will not fight against the dog.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_221">
        <text>Our girl is afraid of doggie. Well, don't be upset.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_3">
        <text>There is a freak in gas-mask. Called Snork. Thin and feeble-looking, but quite agile, no worse than Jackie Chan. I saw a couple of his flicks when a child.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_300">
        <text>The official part is over. Welcome to the lounge.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_31">
        <text>Bring on your snork.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_32">
        <text>No, don't want to fight the snork.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_321">
        <text>Got scared to be dishonoured by a half-rotten gas-masked freak?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_4">
        <text>This time we've got true luck. We caught a young bloodsucker. Still dumb, but already with all the bad manners inherited as proper.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_41">
        <text>Go ahead, get the bloodsucker ready.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_42">
        <text>No, don't want fighting against the bloodsucker.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_421">
        <text>Aha! Got scared. This is what I was suspecting.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_5">
        <text>This time we've got a little midget in black cloack - burer.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_51">
        <text>Bring this one out.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_52">
        <text>No, don't want fighting against the burer.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_521">
        <text>He's hardly reaching your weist in height. And this one made you scared?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_6">
        <text>It's a special day we have. Don't know where they caught him, but it's a true beast. And this is the way they call him - Beast.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_61">
        <text>Deal. Give me the Beast.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_62">
        <text>No, Beast is too much.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_game_621">
        <text>Well, frankly this beast is spooky even for me. But I never go to fight on arena as well, so who's being coward here?\n</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_info_0">
        <text>Got a couple of questions.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_info_1">
        <text>Shoot.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_info_10">
        <text>No more questions here.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_info_11">
        <text>What's the establishment?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_info_111">
        <text>This is my business in the area here. Arena is a place where any stalker will be able to test his forces in a duel with mutants. And if the stalker is skillful enough - he can earn some money as well. Excitement is something even stalkers possess. About a year and a half ago I was cleansing a nest of bloodsuckers with a friend of mine. We ran the last one, a full-grown one into a house, got all the exits blocked, then sat down waiting. And then my friend utters - I bet I do him in within 2 minutes. He entered the dwelling and did him in. That was the moment when the idea originated. We made a deal with the Duty, grabbed a hangar to make an arena out of it. Now we have our own business in the Zone.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_info_12">
        <text>How do live mutants appear here?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_info_121">
        <text>We made a deal with the Duty. Previously they killed everyone when cleansing, but later I proposed them money in exchange for injured weakened mutants. We reached agreement fast. From that moment on I have a virtually never-ending source of live mutants. Later I get the bodies stuffed to sell beyond the zone limits. They are extremely popular.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_info_13">
        <text>Where are you from?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_info_131">
        <text>Where from? From many places. I don't even know what to consider my homeland. A long time I spent in Africa, then several years in Ecuador. And then I heard about this cute place and understood that I can earn a good penny here.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_rules_0">
        <text>What are the rules?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_rules_1">
        <text>Oh, the rules are pretty simple. I invented them myself. There's a cage, and a mutant is let inside the cage. You pay money, so as choose a time you need to kill the monster. If you make it - you get the win. If you don't cope with it - I keep the money. Should you die - I oblige to bury you with all the ceremonies as proper. The less is the time you choose, the bigger is the win.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_start_11">
        <text>Hi there! I've got a new pet. Wanna try your forces against it?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_start_21">
        <text>So, what are you waiting for? Get into the cage, come on.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_start_31">
        <text>Sorry, there's noone to fight against yet. Wait for a day or two until we can catch a new mutant.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_start_41">
        <text>There you are! Well done! Get your win. If you desire another fight for money - drop in.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_arena_manager_start_51">
        <text>Sorry, bro, but you lose. Come again next time if you want.</text>
    </string>
<!------------------ bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader ----------->
	<string id="bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_start_dialog_11">
		<text>Oh, hello. What's up?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_start_dialog_12">
		<text>What do you need, stalker?.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_start_dialog_13">
		<text>You here to buy some shit?</text>
	</string>
<!------------------------- bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic ------------------------>
	<string id="bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_start_dialog_1">
		<text>Hey guy, how goes the Zone? So...I hope you have repair work that needs done...Heh, I need some cash bad.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
