<string_table>
	
	<!-- --------------->
	<!----- ADDONS ----->
	<!------------------>

	<string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_1p29">
        <text>1P29</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_1p29_descr">
        <text>The 1P29 is a medium to long range telescopic sight designed primarily for Kalashnikov-style rifles.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_ac10632">
        <text>Barska AC10632</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_ac10632_descr">
        <text>The Barska AC10632 is a short range high performance reflex sight, however it boasts extremely high visibility due to a large lens and thin frame..</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_ac11090">
        <text>Barska AC11090</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_ac11090_descr">
        <text>The Barska AC11090 is a medium range cheap tube-style optical sight with decent visibility, it is most useful when attached to a shotgun when firing slug rounds.</text>
	</string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_acog">
        <text>Trijicon ACOG</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_acog_descr">
        <text>The Trijicon ACOG is a long range telescopic sight intended for much greater accuracy and visibility on targets at great distance.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_c-more">
        <text>C-MORE</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_c-more_descr">
        <text>The C-MORE is a short range high performance reflex sight with great visibility.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_docter_sight">
        <text>DOCTER</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_docter_sight_descr">
        <text>The DOCTER is a short range reflex sight often attached to pistols for increased accuracy.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_eot">
        <text>EOTech 512</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_eot_descr">
        <text>The EOTech 512 is a very common short to medium range reflex sight with good visibility.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_ekp">
        <text>Kobra EKP-8-02</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_ekp_descr">
        <text>The Kobra EKP-8-02 is a short range reflex sight with decent visibility. Exclusively used by eastern weaponry.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_kobra">
        <text>Kobra EKP-1S-03</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_kobra_descr">
        <text>The Kobra EKP-1S-03 sight is a short to medium range reflex sight with great visibility. Exclusively used by eastern weaponry.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_po4x34">
        <text>Kronos PO 4x34</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_po4x34_descr">
        <text>The Kronos PO 4x34 is a long-range telescopic sight which has largely been replaced by the PSO and its variants.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_pso">
        <text>PSO-1</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_pso_descr">
        <text>The PSO-1 is a long range telescopic sight designed primarily for Kalashnikov-style rifles.</text>
    </string>
	
	<string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_pso1m">
        <text>PSO-1M2</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_pso1m_descr">
        <text>The PSO-1M2 is a variant of the PSO long range telescopic sight, and is designed for use with 9x39 calibre rifles.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_pu">
        <text>PU</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_addon_sight_pu_descr">
        <text>The PU is a telescopic sight designed primarily for World War II era Soviet weaponry.</text>
    </string>
	
	<!-------------------------->
	<!----- VANILLA SCOPES ----->
	<!-------------------------->

	<string id="st_dxr_addon_scope_descr">
		<text>A common Soviet-made 5.0x fixed zoom optical scope with a range scale. Attached to weapons by means of a dovetail mount, which is standard in Warsaw Pact countries.\n \n%c[255,255,255,0]Unused because of an installed weapon pack.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_dxr_addon_scope_detector_descr">
		<text>A 5.0x fixed zoom optical scope with a built-in heat visor used to identify heat sources typical of the human body. Designed for use by special forces. Attached to weapons by means of a dovetail mount.\n \n%c[255,255,255,0]Unused because of an installed weapon pack.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_dxr_addon_scope_night_vision_descr">
		<text>An image intensifier night vision 5.0x fixed zoom scope for combat in darkness. Attached to weapons by means of a dovetail mount.\n \n%c[255,255,255,0]Unused because of an installed weapon pack.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_dxr_addon_scope_susat_custom_descr">
		<text>An adjustable long-range 1.6-4x zoom scope that can use automatic adjustment to provide greater fire effectiveness. Attached to weapons by means of the NATO-standard Picatinny rail.\n \n%c[255,255,255,0]Unused because of an installed weapon pack.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_dxr_addon_scope_susat_descr">
		<text>A 4x fixed zoom scope produced primarily in Western countries. Attached to weapons by means of the NATO-standard Picatinny rail. Often used for accurate fire from small arms at medium to long range.\n \n%c[255,255,255,0]Unused because of an installed weapon pack.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_dxr_addon_scope_susat_dusk_descr">
		<text>An optical SUSAT 1.6x higher contrast scope for combat in reduced lighting conditions. Attached to weapons by means of the NATO-standard Picatinny rail.\n \n%c[255,255,255,0]Unused because of an installed weapon pack.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_dxr_addon_scope_susat_night_vision_descr">
		<text>A 4.0x fixed zoom scope with a night vision device for long range combat in darkness. Attached to weapons by means of the NATO-standard Picatinny rail.\n \n%c[255,255,255,0]Unused because of an installed weapon pack.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_dxr_addon_scope_susat_x1.6_descr">
		<text>An optical SUSAT 1.6x scope for combat at short to medium range. Attached to weapons by means of the NATO-standard Picatinny rail.\n \n%c[255,255,255,0]Unused because of an installed weapon pack.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_dxr_addon_scope_x2.7_descr">
		<text>A 2.7x optical scope for urban combat at medium range. Attached to weapons by means of a dovetail mount.\n \n%c[255,255,255,0]Unused because of an installed weapon pack.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- --------------->
	<!----- KNIVES ----->
	<!------------------>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_knife_survival">
        <text>Survival knife</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_knife_survival_descr">
        <text>A short non-folding survival knife. Easy to conceal due to its small size. A rubber gripped handle allows for improved handling.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_knife_spetsnaz">
        <text>NR-2</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_knife_spetsnaz_descr">
        <text>A military survival knife manufactured for the Spetsnaz during the Soviet era. The NR-2 is a variant of the NRS-2 but lacking the single-shot shooting mechanism.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_knife_tanto">
        <text>Tanto</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_knife_tanto_descr">
        <text>A modern tanto-style combat knife. Literally meaning "short knife", a tanto is a Japanese blade from the feudal era. The origin of this knife is unknown as it is unbranded.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_knife_colt">
        <text>Colt 62316</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_knife_colt_descr">
        <text>The Colt 62316 is an American military M7 bayonet intended to be fixed to the end of a rifle or shotgun. Introduced in 1964, it first saw service in the Vietnam War.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_knife_extrema">
        <text>Extrema Ratio MK 2.1</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_knife_extrema_descr">
        <text>The Extrema Ratio MK 2.1 is a steel knife based on the historic USMC Ka-Bar. Developed and produced for use by the Italian military and special forces.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_knife_hunting">
        <text>Hunting knife</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_knife_hunting_descr">
        <text>A modern hunting knife with a camouflage pattern. Roughly half a dozen barbs run along the top of the blade, making its removal from flesh very difficult.</text>
    </string>
	
	<!-- ----------------->
	<!----- GRENADES ----->
	<!-------------------->
	
    <string id="st_dxr_grenade_f1">
        <text>F1</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_grenade_f1_descr">
        <text>The F1 is a Soviet anti-personnel grenade based on a French grenade of the same name. Designed for defensive use, it relies more on its explosive damage than fragmentation. Due to its lemon-like shape it is nicknamed the "Limonka".</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_grenade_rgd5">
        <text>RGD-5</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_grenade_rgd5_descr">
        <text>The RGD-5 was designed in the early 1950s and later accepted into service by the Soviet Union and its client states. Unlike the F1, the RGD-5 relies on massive fragmentation to kill, rather than its explosive ability.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_grenade_gd-05">
        <text>RDG-M</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_grenade_gd-05_descr">
        <text>The RDG-M is a smoke grenade which creates a small smoke screen for roughly 10 to 15 seconds. Useful for creating temporary cover, smoking enemies out of theirs, or to assist with flanking manoeuvres.</text>
    </string>
	
	<!-- ---------------->
	<!----- PISTOLS ----->
	<!------------------->
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aps_name">
        <text>Stechkin APS</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aps_descr">
        <text>The Stechkin APS is a Soviet selective fire machine pistol. It was developed in the early 1950s by Igor Stechkin and has seen service in conflicts all over the world from Vietnam to eastern Ukraine.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_beretta_name">
        <text>Beretta 92</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_beretta_descr">
        <text>The Beretta 92 is an Italian 9mm pistol that was originally produced from 1976 to 1983. Many variants of the pistol are still produced and used by law enforcement and armed forces the world over even today.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_colt1911_name">
        <text>Colt M1911</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_colt1911_descr">
        <text>The Colt M1911 is an iconic pistol from the early 20th century, and has since found itself involved in almost every major conflict including both World War I and World War II.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_colt_kimber_name">
        <text>Kimber Desert Warrior</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_colt_kimber_descr">
        <text>The Kimber Desert Warrior is an M1911 style semi-automatic pistol based on a special version of the Kimber Custom. The pistol has a matte black KimPro finish and a standard Kimber Custom trigger.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_cz75_name">
        <text>CZ 75</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_cz75_descr">
        <text>The CZ 75 is Czech pistol first introduced in 1975, it is one of the original "wonder nines" featuring a staggered-column magazine, all-steel construction, and a hammer forged barrel.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_desert_eagle_name">
        <text>IMI Desert Eagle</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_desert_eagle_descr">
        <text>The IMI Desert Eagle, also known as the "Deagle", is an Israeli semi-automatic pistol. Whilst it is largely bulky and impractical in the real world, it has found popularity and fame on the big screen, being featured in over 500 motion pictures.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_desert_eagle_nimble_name">
        <text>"Steppe Eagle"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_desert_eagle_nimble_descr">
        <text>This modified IMI Desert Eagle features a silver finish and boasts slightly increased accuracy over the standard model. A DOCTER sight has been mounted to the top of pistol allowing for much greater accuracy at distance and in low-light conditions.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_gsh18_name">
        <text>GSh-18</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_gsh18_descr">
        <text>The GSh-18 is a 9mm semi-automatic pistol developed by the KBP Instrument Design Bureau in Tula during the 1990s. Its name is derived from its designers, Gryazev and Shipunov, and the number 18 denotes the magazine capacity.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fn57_name">
        <text>FN Five-seveN</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fn57_descr">
        <text>The FN Five-seveN is a semi-automatic pistol designed and manufactured by FN Herstal in Belgium. The pistol was developed in conjunction with the FN P90 and the FN 5.7x28mm cartridge.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_glock_name">
        <text>Glock 17</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_glock_descr">
        <text>The Glock series of pistols are unique in that they are largely made of plastic parts. Despite this unorthodox design decision they make up over 65% of the handgun market share for law enforcement agencies in the United States.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fort_name">
        <text>Fort-12</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fort_descr">
        <text>The Fort-12 is a semi-automatic pistol which was designed in the late 1990s by Ukrainian firearms designer RPC Fort.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fort_snag_name">
        <text>Fort-17</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fort_snag_descr">
        <text>The Fort-17 is a semi-automatic pistol which was designed in the late 1990s by Ukrainian firearms designer RPC Fort. This variant of the pistol has a magazine capacity of 17 rounds.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fnp45_name">
        <text>FN FNP-45</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fnp45_descr">
        <text>The FN FNP-45 is from the FNP series of semi-automatic, polymer-framed pistols manufactured by FN America. As the name would imply, it is chambered to fire the .45 ACP round.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fnx45_name">
        <text>FN FNX-45 Tactical</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fnx45_descr">
        <text>A heavily modified FN FNX-45, this pistol is affixed with a DOCTER sight and suppressor. The weapon and its attachments are covered in a tan paint-job, however the lack of sandy environments in the Zone brings into question its usefulness.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_hpsa_name">
        <text>Browning Hi-Power</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_hpsa_descr">
        <text>The Browning Hi-Power is an American handgun based on designs by John Browning. First brought into production in 1935, this particular model of the weapon is chambered to fire 9mm cartridges.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_mp443_name">
        <text>MP-443 Grach</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_mp443_descr">
        <text>The MP-443 Grach is a Russian pistol developed in response to Russian military trials. It was later adopted as a standard side-arm for all branches of the Russian military and law enforcement.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_oc33_name">
        <text>OTs-33 "Pernach"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_oc33_descr">
        <text>The OTs-33 "Pernach" is an automatic pistol designed to replace the Stechkin APS because of huge recoil when fired in fully automatic. It is currently used by units of the Russian police and the MVD.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_pb_name">
        <text>PB</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_pb_descr">
        <text>The PB is a Soviet suppressed pistol based on the design of the Makarov PM and was issued into service in 1967. The pistol may be fired safely without the additional suppressor attachment.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_pm_name">
        <text>Makarov PM</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_pm_descr">
        <text>The Makarov PM is a Russian semi-automatic pistol. It became the Soviet Union's standard military and police side-arm from 1951 to 1991 after replacing the Tokarev TT-33.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_pm_actor_name">
        <text>Ceremonial Makarov PM</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_pm_actor_descr">
        <text>A ceremonial Makarov PM once awarded to Major Degtyarev as the engraving on the side would suggest. How it ended up in the Zone and how it fell out of his possession is unknown.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_pmm_name">
        <text>Makarov PMM</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_pmm_descr">
        <text>The Makarov PMM is modernised version of the Makarov PM. The most notable difference is the greater magazine capacity, being able to hold four additional rounds.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_sig220_name">
        <text>SIG Sauer P220</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_sig220_descr">
        <text>The SIG Sauer P220 is a semi-automatic pistol developed in 1975 for the Swiss Army as a replacement for the P210.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_tt33_name">
        <text>Tokarev TT-33</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_tt33_descr">
        <text>The TT-33 is a Russian semi-automatic pistol developed in the early 1930s to replace the Nagant M1895 revolver. The design was simplified from the TT-30's to make it easier to manufacture.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_usp_name">
        <text>H&amp;K USP .45</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_usp_descr">
        <text>The USP is a semi-automatic pistol developed by Heckler &amp; Koch as a replacement for the P7 series of handguns. One of the most significant features of the USP is the mechanical recoil reduction system.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_usp_nimble_name">
        <text>H&amp;K USP Match</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_usp_nimble_descr">
        <text>The USP Match is specifically designed to appeal to target shooters. The Match distinguishes itself by its barrel weight, which provides counterbalance to the weapon's recoil, greatly improving follow up target tracking.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_walther_name">
        <text>Walther P99</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_walther_descr">
        <text>The Walther P99 is a semi-automatic pistol developed for law enforcement, security forces and the civilian shooting market as a replacement for the Walther P5 and the P88.</text>
    </string>
	
	<!-- --------------->
	<!----- RIFLES ----->
	<!------------------>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_9a91_name">
        <text>9A-91</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_9a91_descr">
        <text>The 9A-91 is a carbine assault rifle designed in the early 1990s and used by Russian police forces. Firing the subsonic 9x39 round in combination with a suppressor attachment can make for a deadly and compact stealth weapon.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_abakan_name">
        <text>AN-94 "Abakan"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_abakan_descr">
        <text>The AN-94 was built as a potential replacement to the AK-74M. Featuring a unique 2-round burst, the rifle is able to fire a second round before the recoil of the first is felt. Because of this the first two shots are often very accurate even at long-range.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ace21_name">
        <text>IWI ACE 21</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ace21_descr">
        <text>The ACE family of assault rifles are based upon the mechanism of the IMI Galil, but using modernised designs and materials to increase accuracy and reduce weight. This model is chambered for 5.56x54mm ammunition.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aek971_name">
        <text>AEK-971</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aek971_descr">
        <text>The AEK-971 is a Soviet selective fire assault rifle that was developed at the Kovrov Mechanical Plant in the late 1970s and 80s. This model fires the 5.45x39mm round used by many Kalashnikov-pattern weapons.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aek973_name">
        <text>AEK-973</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aek973_descr">
        <text>The AEK-973 is a Soviet selective fire assault rifle that was developed at the Kovrov Mechanical Plant in the late 1970s and 80s. This model fires the 7.62x39mm round used by many Kalashnikov-pattern weapons.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak101_name">
        <text>AK-101</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak101_descr">
        <text>The AK-101 is designed for the world export market and is marketed at those looking for a weapon that combines the familiarity of the 5.56x45mm NATO round with the reliability of a Kalashnikov.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak102_name">
        <text>AK-102</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak102_descr">
        <text>The AK-102 is a shortened carbine version of the AK-101 and is marketed at those looking for a weapon that combines the familiarity of the 5.56x45mm NATO round with the reliability of a Kalashnikov.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak103_name">
        <text>AK-103</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak103_descr">
        <text>The AK-103 is a derivative of the AK-74M, notably replacing wooden parts for plastic wherever possible. It is chambered for the 7.62x39mm round similar to the AKM.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak104_name">
        <text>AK-104</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak104_descr">
        <text>The AK-104 is a shortened carbine version of the AK-103. It is chambered for the 7.62x39mm round similar to the AKM.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak105_name">
        <text>AK-105</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak105_descr">
        <text>The AK-105 is a shortened carbine version of the AK-74M, which offers more versatility when compared to its predecessors.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak12_name">
        <text>AK-12</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak12_descr">
        <text>The AK-12 is the newest derivative of the Kalashnikov-pattern series of assault rifles and was proposed for possible general issue to the Russian Army. This model has been chambered to fire the 5.45x39mm cartridge.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak15_name">
        <text>AK-15</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak15_descr">
        <text>The AK-15 is the newest derivative of the Kalashnikov-pattern series of assault rifles and was proposed for possible general issue to the Russian Army. This model has been chambered to fire the 7.62x39mm cartridge.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak47_name">
        <text>AK-47</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak47_descr">
        <text>The AK-47 was first brought into production shortly after World War II, and by 1949 the rifle was adopted by the Soviet Union and most of the Warsaw Pact forces. Even after almost seven decades, the model and its variants remain the most popular and widely used assault rifles in the world.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74_name">
        <text>AK-74</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74_descr">
        <text>The AK-74 is an assault rifle developed in the early 1970s by Mikhail Kalashnikov as the replacement for the earlier AKM. It uses a smaller 5.45x39mm cartridge, replacing the 7.62x39mm chambering of earlier Kalashnikovs.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74_descr2">
        <text>The AK-74 is an assault rifle developed in the early 1970s by Mikhail Kalashnikov as the replacement for the earlier AKM. It uses a smaller 5.45x39mm cartridge, replacing the 7.62x39mm chambering of earlier Kalashnikovs.\n \n%c[255,255,255,0]This variant lacks a mount to attach optics.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74_up_name">
        <text>Vaska's AK-74</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74_up_descr">
        <text>A modified AK-74 rifle long ago found on the corpse of Vaska Kuzin, a soldier stationed in the Cordon. It has an EOTech 512 optical sight fitted via an MTK-83 mount, a 45-round magazine taken from an RPK-74 and a suppressor.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74_up2_name">
        <text>AK-74 Tactical</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74_up2_descr">
        <text>The most notable difference with this AK-74 is that the upper hand-guard has been removed and an Aimpoint Micro T-1 optical sight fitted in its place. A darker paint-job covers the weapon components, perhaps to make it more difficult to spot after dark.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74m_name">
        <text>AK-74M</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74m_descr">
        <text>The AK-74M offers more versatility when compared to its predecessors. The rifle features a side-rail bracket for mounting optics, an improved muzzle device and a reinforced smooth dust cover.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74m_nimble_name">
        <text>AK-74M Tactical</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74m_nimble_descr">
        <text>A woodland camouflage pattern and a unique PK-A optical sight adorn this rifle. It is obvious that its original owner must have been a professional stalker, although there is little to no indication left as to who that was.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74m_raifu_name">
        <text>"Raifu"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74m_raifu_descr">
        <text>This particular rifle with an eccentric paint job was recovered from a laboratory hidden deep within the Zone. The expedition group found the rifle together with its previous owner, an overweight stalker, who held the rifle close to himself as he stared into a broken computer screen.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74u_name">
        <text>AKS-74U</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74u_descr">
        <text>The AKS-74U is a shortened carbine version of the AK-74, with its shorter length making it better for close quarters and indoor combat. The rifle was likely developed in response to the CAR-15 Commando which was used by the US in the Vietnam War.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74u_descr2">
        <text>The AKS-74U is a shortened carbine version of the AK-74, with its shorter length making it better for close quarters and indoor combat. The rifle was likely developed in response to the CAR-15 Commando which was used by the US in the Vietnam War.\n \n%c[255,255,255,0]This variant lacks a mount to attach optics.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74u_snag_name">
        <text>AKS-74U Tactical</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74u_snag_descr">
        <text>All wooden parts on this rifle have been replaced with plastic and other light composite materials. A Kobra optic and a PBS-4 suppressor have been fitted to the weapon, all of which have been painted black.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aks47_name">
        <text>AKS-47</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aks47_descr">
        <text>Designed for use in the restricted space of the BMP infantry combat vehicle, as well as by paratroopers, the AKS is a folding-stock variant of the AK-47 assault rifle which was developed in the late 1940s.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aks74_name">
        <text>AKS-74</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aks74_descr">
        <text>The AKS-74 is a variant of the AK-74 equipped with a side-folding metal shoulder stock, designed primarily for use with air assault infantry.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_akm_name">
        <text>AKM</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_akm_descr">
        <text>The AKM is a modernised variant of the AK-47 assault rifle which was designed and brought into service in the late 1950s. It was one of the last Kalashnikov-pattern rifles designed to fire the 7.62x39mm round.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_akms_name">
        <text>AKMS</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_akms_descr">
        <text>The AKMS is a side-folding metal stock variant of the AKM assault rifle designed for airborne military units, much like the AKS-47 and AKS-74..</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aug_name">
        <text>Steyr AUG A1</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aug_descr">
        <text>The Steyr AUG A1 is an Austrian bullpup assault rifle designed in the 1960s. In production since 1978, it is the standard small arm of the Austrian Bundesheer and various national police units.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_bizon_name">
        <text>PP-19 Bizon-2</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_bizon_descr">
        <text>The Bizon was developed for counter-terrorist and law enforcement units that usually need fast and accurate fire at close ranges. It uses an unusual 64-round helical-feed magazine that mounts under the handguard in line with the barrel making the weapon more compact and concealable.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_bizon201_name">
        <text>PP-19 Bizon-2-01</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_bizon201_descr">
        <text>The Bizon-2-01 variant is chambered for the 9x19mm cartridge using a modified helical-feed magazine with a 53-round capacity. Like the standard model, the magazine mounts under the handguard in line with the barrel making the weapon more compact and concealable.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_bm16_name">
        <text>TOZ-66 (Obrez)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_bm16_descr">
        <text>The TOZ-66 is a break-action double-barrel shotgun produced between 1968 and 1974 and uses a side-by-side barrel configuration. This particular shotgun has had the majority of the barrel and stock sawed off.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_bm16_full_name">
        <text>TOZ-66</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_bm16_full_descr">
        <text>The TOZ-66 is a break-action double-barrel shotgun produced between 1968 and 1974 and uses a side-by-side barrel configuration.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_famas_name">
        <text>FAMAS F1</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_famas_descr">
        <text>The FAMAS is a bullpup-style assault rifle designed and manufactured in France between 1975 and 2000. Almost 40 years on from its initial production, the FAMAS F1 and G2 variants are still used by the French military.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fn2000_name">
        <text>FN F2000</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fn2000_descr">
        <text>The F2000 is a gas operated, fully automatic and ambidextrous bullpup rifle developed by FN Herstal. The weapon has a telescopic sight with a fixed 1.6x magnification contained within a plastic housing above the receiver.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fnc_name">
        <text>FN FNC</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fnc_descr">
        <text>The FN FNC is an assault rifle developed by FN Herstal and introduced in the late 1970s. The rifle's design is based on the FNC 76 prototype, which itself originated from the commercially unsuccessful FN CAL rifle.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_g3_name">
        <text>H&amp;K G3</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_g3_descr">
        <text>The G3 is a 7.62x51mm chambered battle rifle developed by H&amp;K in collaboration with CETME. The origin of this rifle can be traced back to the final years of World War II when Mauser engineers designed the MKb Gerat 06</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_g36_name">
        <text>H&amp;K G36</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_g36_descr">
        <text>The G36 is an assault rifle designed in the early 1990s by Heckler &amp; Koch in Germany as a replacement for the heavier G3 battle rifle.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_g36_nimble_name">
        <text>XM8</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_g36_nimble_descr">
        <text>Based on the G36, the XM8 was originally part of the OICW program, but after being unable to meet performance and weight requirements was eventually cancelled. It is unclear how a rifle such as this ended up in the Zone.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_g36c_name">
        <text>H&amp;K G36C</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_g36c_descr">
        <text>The G36C is a compact variant of the G36 assault rifle. It features a much shortened barrel, handguard and stock, and an integrated rail for optical sights.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_g36k_name">
        <text>H&amp;K G36K</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_g36k_descr">
        <text>The G36K is a carbine variant of the G36 assault rifle. This model of the weapon has an integrated 3x magnification scope replacing the red-dot optical sights.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_g3a3_name">
        <text>H&amp;K G3A3</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_g3a3_descr">
        <text>The G3A3 is a selective-fire automatic battle rifle and most well-known variant of the G3. It features drum sights, a fixed plastic buttstock, and a plastic handguard that does not contact the barrel.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_g3sg1_name">
        <text>H&amp;K G3SG1</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_g3sg1_descr">
        <text>Also known as the HSG1, this variant is a Luxemburg-produced marksman model of the battle rifle. Modifications to the handguard allow for a tripod to be attached for greater stability.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_galil_name">
        <text>IMI Galil BR</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_galil_descr">
        <text>A battle rifle variant of the Galil assault rifle chambered to fire 7.62x51mm ammunition. The rifle was designed in the late 1960s by Yisrael Galili and Yaacov Lior, and takes its name from the former.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_galil_ar_name">
        <text>IMI Galil</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_galil_ar_descr">
        <text>The Galil is an Israeli assault rifle designed by Yisrael Galili and Yaacov Lior in the late 1960s, and takes its name from the former. Many variants and adaptations of the weapon exist, such as the IWI ACE family of rifles.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_gauss_name">
        <text>Gauss rifle</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_gauss_descr">
        <text>Officially "Item 62", this unusual weapon was created by researchers and weaponsmiths within the Zone. The current design is based on the EM1, which was captured from Clear Sky by the Monolith.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_groza_name">
        <text>OTs-14-4A "Groza-4"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_groza_descr">
        <text>The Groza-4 is a Russian selective fire bullpup assault rifle chambered for the 9x39mm subsonic round. It was developed in the 1990s at the TsKIB SOO in Tula, Russia.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_groza1_name">
        <text>OTs-14-1A "Groza-1"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_groza1_descr">
        <text>The Groza-1 is a Russian selective fire bullpup assault rifle, the 1A/Groza-1 variant is chambered for the 5.45x39mm round. It was developed in the 1990s at the TsKIB SOO in Tula, Russia.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_hk416_name">
        <text>H&amp;K HK416</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_hk416_descr">
        <text>The HK416 is an assault rifle designed and manufactured by Heckler &amp; Koch based on the AR-15 platform. It is used by police forces, special forces and armed forces in many Western nations.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_l85_name">
        <text>L85A2</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_l85_descr">
        <text>The L85A2 is a British selective fire, gas-operated assault rifle and member of the SA80 weapons family. Its bullpup design and mounted SUSAT sight keep the weapon compact without sacrificing accuracy.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_l96_name">
        <text>L96A1</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_l96_descr">
        <text>The L96A1 is a bolt-action sniper rifle designed and manufactured by the British company Accuracy International. It has proved popular as a civilian, police, and military rifle since its introduction in the 1980s.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_lr300_name">
        <text>LR-300 ML-N</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_l96_descr">
        <text>Designed and manufactured by Z-M Weapons, the LR-300 is an American assault rifle and conversion kit. The ML-N variant has an 11.53-inch barrel, Nylatron forend with attachable Picatinny rails, and fires single shots or bursts</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_m16_name">
        <text>M16</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_m16_descr">
        <text>One of the most iconic rifles ever produced, the M16 entered American military service in 1964 and the following year was deployed for jungle warfare operations during the Vietnam War. Since then around 8 million unit have been produced.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_m16a2_name">
        <text>M16A2</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_m16a2_descr">
        <text>Based on the M16, the M16A2 was adopted by the US Department of Defence in 1982 following combat experience in Vietnam. With new rifling, a thicker barrel and an adjustable rear sight - the M16A2 is a notable upgrade.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_m249_name">
        <text>M249 SAW</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_m249_descr">
        <text>The M249 is the American adaptation of the Belgian FN Minimi, a light machine gun manufactured by the Belgian company FN Herstal.  The weapon was introduced in 1984 after being judged the most effective of a number of candidate weapons to address the lack of automatic firepower in small units.</text>
    </string>
	
</string_table>