<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
<!--------------------------- mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor -->
	<string id="mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_start_1">
		<text>What brings you here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_need_health_care_0">
		<text>I need medical assistance.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_need_health_care_1">
		<text>Alright, I'll see what I can do.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_need_health_care_2">
		<text>Alright, I'll take a look... No wounds? You show no signs of radiation sickness. I think everything is in order; You are good to go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_need_health_care_11">
		<text>[continue...]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_need_health_care_111">
		<text>That wasn't so bad, eh? You can go.</text>
	</string>
<!--------------------------- marsh_stalker_barmen -->
	<string id="marsh_stalker_barmen_start_dialog_1">
		<text>A fresh face! People around here call me Cold. I'm the local bartender. I'll be glad to answer any questions you have. Sometimes I post job offerings or hear some interesting rumours, so check back often.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="marsh_stalker_barmen_start_dialog_2">
		<text>Hey, stalker. What do you need?</text>
	</string>
<!--------------------------- mar_base_owl_stalker_trader -->
	<string id="mar_base_owl_stalker_trader_start_dialog_1">
		<text>Need supplies or equipment? Information?... Or maybe you want to sell information?</text>
	</string>
<!---------------------------- marsh_stalker_tech --->
	<string id="marsh_stalker_tech_start_1">
		<text>Greetings, stalker. Can I be of assistance? Good tools are hard to come by in the Zone, but I can still repair your kit and do minor upgrades.</text>
	</string>
	 <string id="cit_doctor_hello_dialog_11">
        <text>Greetings stranger! Did you meet Strelok? I haven't seen him since the last raid, which was years ago! I'm worried!</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_hello_dialog_21">
        <text>I told you everything what I know. Peace, man.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_0">
        <text>Strelok? Nope, I didn't see him, he is disappeared since years. But as far I know, you know a lot of secrets of the Zone.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_1">
        <text>Sorry to hear that. We went into the Zone together with Strelok for 2 years. Yeah, I know this and that about the Zone.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_11">
        <text>What exactly you know?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_2">
        <text>I tell it, if you search for me Fang and Ghost. I haven't seen them for years.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_21">
        <text>You must be joking, or you are living under a rock too long. These guys fate are in legends since years. Ghost is dead - someone found his body in Yantar. Fang was shot by Scar with a Vintar in Army Warehouses.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_3">
        <text>Ghost!!?!?! Dead??!!! Fang !!?!? Dammit, how could that happen?! They... they were the best. Okay, I tell you what I know.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_31">
        <text>Really? So easy? I feel you are just wasting my time, old man.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_4">
        <text>Wait, and calm down. That's some shitty news man. I think it's all linked with Strelok's last trip into the Zone. When we saw each other the last time, Strelok left me the key from the stash at Pripyat and the map of how to find it. I've managed to keep it and hid it. Here, take it, hide it well. Perhaps you'll find something there. Strelok was saying that there's some trick with the Monolith. But I don't understand what it was about, and Strelok didn't either.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_41">
        <text>I see. Thanks, I appreciate your cooperation and help.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_5">
        <text>Now get out of here, stalker.</text>
    </string>
</string_table>
