<string_table>

	<!-- The texts in this file are used by the official weapon pack addons. -->
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aps_name">
        <text>Stechkin APS</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aps_descr">
        <text>The Stechkin APS is a Soviet selective fire machine pistol. It was developed in the early 1950s by Igor Stechkin and has seen service in conflicts all over the world from Vietnam to eastern Ukraine.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_beretta_name">
        <text>Beretta 92</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_beretta_descr">
        <text>The Beretta 92 is an Italian 9mm pistol that was originally produced from 1976 to 1983. Many variants of the pistol are still produced and used by law enforcement and armed forces the world over even today.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_colt1911_name">
        <text>Colt M1911</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_colt1911_descr">
        <text>The Colt M1911 is an iconic pistol from the early 20th century, and has since found itself involved in almost every major conflict including both World War I and World War II.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_colt_kimber_name">
        <text>Kimber Desert Warrior</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_colt_kimber_descr">
        <text>The Kimber Desert Warrior is an M1911 style semi-automatic pistol based on a special version of the Kimber Custom. The pistol has a matte black KimPro finish and a standard Kimber Custom trigger.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_cz75_name">
        <text>CZ 75</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_cz75_auto_name">
        <text>CZ 75 Automatic</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_cz75_descr">
        <text>The CZ 75 is Czech pistol first introduced in 1975, it is one of the original "wonder nines" featuring a staggered-column magazine, all-steel construction, and a hammer forged barrel.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_desert_eagle_name">
        <text>IMI Desert Eagle</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_desert_eagle_descr">
        <text>The IMI Desert Eagle, also known as the "Deagle", is an Israeli semi-automatic pistol. Whilst it is largely bulky and impractical in the real world, it has found popularity and fame on the big screen, being featured in over 500 motion pictures.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_desert_eagle_nimble_name">
        <text>"Steppe Eagle"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_desert_eagle_nimble_descr">
        <text>This modified IMI Desert Eagle features a silver finish and boasts slightly increased accuracy over the standard model. A DOCTER sight has been mounted to the top of pistol allowing for much greater accuracy at distance and in low-light conditions.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_gsh18_name">
        <text>GSh-18</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_gsh18_descr">
        <text>The GSh-18 is a 9mm semi-automatic pistol developed by the KBP Instrument Design Bureau in Tula during the 1990s. Its name is derived from its designers, Gryazev and Shipunov, and the number 18 denotes the magazine capacity.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fn57_name">
        <text>FN Five-seven</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fn57_descr">
        <text>The FN Five-seven is a semi-automatic pistol designed and manufactured by FN Herstal in Belgium. The pistol was developed in conjunction with the FN P90 and the FN 5.7x28mm cartridge.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_glock_name">
        <text>Glock 17</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_glock_descr">
        <text>The Glock series of pistols are unique in that they are largely made of plastic parts. Despite this unorthodox design decision they make up over 65% of the handgun market share for law enforcement agencies in the United States.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fort_name">
        <text>Fort-12</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fort_descr">
        <text>The Fort-12 is a semi-automatic pistol which was designed in the late 1990s by Ukrainian firearms designer RPC Fort.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fort_snag_name">
        <text>Fort-17</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fort_snag_descr">
        <text>The Fort-17 is a semi-automatic pistol which was designed in the late 1990s by Ukrainian firearms designer RPC Fort. This variant of the pistol has a magazine capacity of 17 rounds.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fnp45_name">
        <text>FN FNP-45</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fnp45_descr">
        <text>The FN FNP-45 is from the FNP series of semi-automatic, polymer-framed pistols manufactured by FN America. As the name would imply, it is chambered to fire the .45 ACP round.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fnx45_name">
        <text>FN FNX-45 Tactical</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_fnx45_descr">
        <text>A heavily modified FN FNX-45, this pistol is affixed with a DOCTER sight and suppressor. The weapon and its attachments are covered in a tan paint-job, however the lack of sandy environments in the Zone brings into question its usefulness.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_hpsa_name">
        <text>Browning Hi-Power</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_hpsa_descr">
        <text>The Browning Hi-Power is an American handgun based on designs by John Browning. First brought into production in 1935, this particular model of the weapon is chambered to fire 9mm cartridges.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_mp443_name">
        <text>MP-443 Grach</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_mp443_descr">
        <text>The MP-443 Grach is a Russian pistol developed in response to Russian military trials. It was later adopted as a standard side-arm for all branches of the Russian military and law enforcement.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_oc33_name">
        <text>OTs-33 Pernach</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_oc33_descr">
        <text>The OTs-33 Pernach is an automatic pistol designed to replace the Stechkin APS because of huge recoil when fired in fully automatic. It is currently used by units of the Russian police and the MVD.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_pb_name">
        <text>PB</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_pb_descr">
        <text>The PB is a Soviet suppressed pistol based on the design of the Makarov PM and was issued into service in 1967. The pistol may be fired safely without the additional suppressor attachment.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_pm_name">
        <text>Makarov PM</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_pm_descr">
        <text>The Makarov PM is a Russian semi-automatic pistol. It became the Soviet Union's standard military and police side-arm from 1951 to 1991 after replacing the Tokarev TT-33.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_pm_actor_name">
        <text>Ceremonial Makarov PM</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_pm_actor_descr">
        <text>A ceremonial Makarov PM once awarded to Major Degtyarev as the engraving on the side would suggest. How it ended up in the Zone and how it fell out of his possession is unknown.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_pmm_name">
        <text>Makarov PMM</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_pmm_descr">
        <text>The Makarov PMM is modernised version of the Makarov PM. The most notable difference is the greater magazine capacity, being able to hold four additional rounds.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_sig220_name">
        <text>SIG Sauer P220</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_sig220_descr">
        <text>The SIG Sauer P220 is a semi-automatic pistol developed in 1975 for the Swiss Army as a replacement for the P210.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_tt33_name">
        <text>Tokarev TT-33</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_tt33_descr">
        <text>The TT-33 is a Russian semi-automatic pistol developed in the early 1930s to replace the Nagant M1895 revolver. The design was simplified from the TT-30's to make it easier to manufacture.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_usp_name">
        <text>H&amp;K USP .45</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_usp_descr">
        <text>The USP is a semi-automatic pistol developed by Heckler &amp; Koch as a replacement for the P7 series of handguns. One of the most significant features of the USP is the mechanical recoil reduction system.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_usp_nimble_name">
        <text>H&amp;K USP Match</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_usp_nimble_descr">
        <text>The USP Match is specifically designed to appeal to target shooters. The Match distinguishes itself by its barrel weight, which provides counterbalance to the weapon's recoil, greatly improving follow up target tracking.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_walther_name">
        <text>Walther P99</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_walther_descr">
        <text>The Walther P99 is a semi-automatic pistol developed for law enforcement, security forces and the civilian shooting market as a replacement for the Walther P5 and the P88.</text>
    </string>
	
</string_table>