<string_table>

	<!-- The texts in this file are used by the official weapon pack addons. -->
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_9a91_name">
        <text>9A-91</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_9a91_descr">
        <text>The 9A-91 is a carbine assault rifle designed in the early 1990s and used by Russian police forces. Firing the subsonic 9x39 round in combination with a suppressor attachment can make for a deadly and compact stealth weapon.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_abakan_name">
        <text>AN-94 "Abakan"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_abakan_descr">
        <text>The AN-94 was built as a potential replacement to the AK-74M. Featuring a unique 2-round burst, the rifle is able to fire a second round before the recoil of the first is felt. Because of this the first two shots are often very accurate even at long-range.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ace21_name">
        <text>IWI ACE 21</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ace21_descr">
        <text>The ACE family of assault rifles are based upon the mechanism of the IMI Galil, but using modernised designs and materials to increase accuracy and reduce weight. This model is chambered for 5.56x54 ammunition.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aek971_name">
        <text>AEK-971</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aek971_descr">
        <text>The AEK-971 is a Soviet selective fire assault rifle that was developed at the Kovrov Mechanical Plant in the late 1970s and 80s. This model fires the 5.45x39 round used by many Kalashnikov-pattern weapons.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak_name">
        <text>AK-47</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak_descr">
        <text>The AK-47 was first brought into production shortly after World War II, and by 1949 the rifle was adopted by the Soviet Union and most of the Warsaw Pact forces. Even after almost seven decades, the model and its variants remain the most popular and widely used assault rifles in the world.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak101_name">
        <text>AK-101</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak101_descr">
        <text>The AK-101 is designed for the world export market and is marketed at those looking for a weapon that combines the familiarity of the 5.56x45 NATO round with the reliability of a Kalashnikov.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak102_name">
        <text>AK-102</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak102_descr">
        <text>The AK-102 is a shortened carbine version of the AK-101 and is marketed at those looking for a weapon that combines the familiarity of the 5.56x45 NATO round with the reliability of a Kalashnikov.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak103_name">
        <text>AK-103</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak103_descr">
        <text>The AK-103 is a derivative of the AK-74M, notably replacing wooden parts for plastic wherever possible. It is chambered for the 7.62x39 round similar to the AKM.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak104_name">
        <text>AK-104</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak104_descr">
        <text>The AK-104 is a shortened carbine version of the AK-103. It is chambered for the 7.62x39 round similar to the AKM.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak105_name">
        <text>AK-105</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak105_descr">
        <text>The AK-105 is a shortened carbine version of the AK-74M, which offers more versatility when compared to its predecessors.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak12_name">
        <text>AK-12</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak12_descr">
        <text>The AK-12 is the newest derivative of the Kalashnikov-pattern series of assault rifles and was proposed for possible general issue to the Russian Army. </text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74_name">
        <text>AK-74</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74_descr">
        <text>The AK-74 is an assault rifle developed in the early 1970s by Mikhail Kalashnikov as the replacement for the earlier AKM. It uses a smaller 5.45x39 cartridge, replacing the 7.62x39 chambering of earlier Kalashnikovs.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74_descr2">
        <text>The AK-74 is an assault rifle developed in the early 1970s by Mikhail Kalashnikov as the replacement for the earlier AKM. It uses a smaller 5.45x39 cartridge, replacing the 7.62x39 chambering of earlier Kalashnikovs.\n \n%c[255,255,255,0]This variant lacks a mount to attach optics.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74_up_name">
        <text>Vaska's AK-74</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74_up_descr">
        <text>A modified AK-74 rifle long ago found on the corpse of Vaska Kuzin, a soldier stationed in the Cordon. It has an EOTech 512 optical sight fitted via an MTK-83 mount, a 45-round magazine taken from an RPK-74 and a suppressor.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74_up2_name">
        <text>AK-74 Tactical</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74_up2_descr">
        <text>The most notable difference with this AK-74 is that the upper hand-guard has been removed and an Aimpoint Micro T-1 optical sight fitted in its place. A darker paint-job covers the weapon components, perhaps to make it more difficult to spot after dark.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74m_name">
        <text>AK-74M</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74m_descr">
        <text>The AK-74M offers more versatility when compared to its predecessors. The rifle features a side-rail bracket for mounting optics, an improved muzzle device and a reinforced smooth dust cover.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74m_camo_name">
        <text>AK-74M Tactical</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74m_camo_descr">
        <text>A woodland camouflage pattern and a unique PK-A optical sight adorn this rifle. It is obvious that its original owner must have been a professional stalker, although there is little to no indication left as to who that was.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74m_raifu_name">
        <text>"Raifu"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74m_raifu_descr">
        <text>This particular rifle with an eccentric paint job was recovered from a laboratory hidden deep within the Zone. The expedition group found the rifle together with its previous owner, an overweight stalker, who held the rifle close to himself as he stared into a broken computer screen.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74u_name">
        <text>AKS-74U</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74u_descr">
        <text>The AKS-74U is a shortened carbine version of the AK-74, with its shorter length making it better for close quarters and indoor combat. The rifle was likely developed in response to the CAR-15 Commando which was used by the US in the Vietnam War.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74u_descr2">
        <text>The AKS-74U is a shortened carbine version of the AK-74, with its shorter length making it better for close quarters and indoor combat. The rifle was likely developed in response to the CAR-15 Commando which was used by the US in the Vietnam War.\n \n%c[255,255,255,0]This variant lacks a mount to attach optics.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74u_snag_name">
        <text>AKS-74U Tactical</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_ak74u_snag_descr">
        <text>All wooden parts on this rifle have been replaced with plastic and other light composite materials. A Kobra optic and a PBS-4 suppressor have been fitted to the weapon, all of which have been painted black.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aks_name">
        <text>AKS-47</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aks_descr">
        <text>Designed for use in the restricted space of the BMP infantry combat vehicle, as well as by paratroopers, the AKS is a folding-stock variant of the AK-47 assault rifle which was developed in the late 1940s.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aks74_name">
        <text>AKS-74</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aks74_descr">
        <text>The AKS-74 is a variant of the AK-74 equipped with a side-folding metal shoulder stock, designed primarily for use with air assault infantry.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_akm_name">
        <text>AKM</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_akm_descr">
        <text>The AKM is a modernised variant of the AK-47 assault rifle which was designed and brought into service in the late 1950s. It was one of the last Kalashnikov-pattern rifles designed to fire the 7.62x39 round.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_akms_name">
        <text>AKMS</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_akms_descr">
        <text>The AKMS is a side-folding metal stock variant of the AKM assault rifle designed for airborne military units, much like the AKS-47 and AKS-74..</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aug_name">
        <text>Steyr AUG A1</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aug_descr">
        <text>The Steyr AUG A1 is an Austrian bullpup assault rifle designed in the 1960s. In production since 1978, it is the standard small arm of the Austrian Bundesheer and various national police units.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aug_a3_name">
        <text>Steyr AUG A3</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_dxr_wpn_aug_a3_descr">
        <text>The A3 model of the Steyr AUG features a redesigned charging handle, a MIL-STD-1913 rail on top of the receiver, and an external bolt release. This specific rifle has been fitted with a Trijicon ACOG.</text>
    </string>
	
</string_table>