<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
<!------------------ bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader ----------->
	<string id="bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_start_dialog_11">
		<text>Oh, hello. What's up?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_start_dialog_12">
		<text>What do you need, stalker?.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_start_dialog_13">
		<text>You here to buy some shit?</text>
	</string>
<!------------------------- bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic ------------------------>
	<string id="bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_start_1111">
		<text>So?... You, err... feel free to bring me all your broken shooters, suits full of holes and whatnot... I ain't half as good when I'm sober, but I'll give it a shot...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_start_1112">
		<text>Where have you been? I was getting worried, looked everywhere for you. Where is that stalker, I said... Cheers, eh?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_start_1113">
		<text>Howdy. Nice of you to come by. Make yourself at home... Did you bring me something to fix or something to drink?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_start_1211">
		<text>Whew! Cool! My hands aren't shaking, but my head says "I want more"... Pour me another one, young man!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_start_1212">
		<text>Why so slow? Open the next bottle, c'mon! Let's drink to our common cause. Yeah. Vodka brings out the mechanic genius in me, I shit you not.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_start_1312">
		<text>I wish Joker was here, we'd drink to Barge together... Well, may he rest in peace. He was good man, a real die-hard. Tough like a rock.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_start_1313">
		<text>I wish Barge was here, we'd drink to Joker together... Well, may he rest in peace. He was a good man, always there for you. Never went back on his word.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_start_1314">
		<text>Uhh... Barge... Joker... How did it all come to this... So, one thing leads to another...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_start_1315">
		<text>Mm-hmm?... What do we got here? I'll deal with the armored SMGs tomorrow... Don't worry, it ain't no thing. Got some good booze waitin'...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_start_14">
		<text>That number sixty two... I'd really like a peek at the circuit schematics.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_start_15">
		<text>A wise choice, my friend. Gotta keep your gun in mint condition. And if you got a bottle or two on you, I can make it upgrade galore in here. Want a parachute sewn to your shotgun? I can do that, hehe.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_start_16">
		<text>Would you look at that! They stuck an electrostatic artifact into the battery! Hah! I knew it was some kind of weird anomalous shit! The principle is a no-brainer - now I can hammer out these cells myself.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_start_17">
		<text>Need some nut-and-bolt work?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_start_18">
		<text>This reads like gibberish. I guess I haven't read technical documents in a while...</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
