<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
    <string id="oso_chernobyl_crush_0">
        <text>Is the explosion of '86 your work too?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_chernobyl_crush_1">
        <text>No, we had nothing to do with that. Most of us were only starting out in science back then. The Chernobyl Zone was not used as a testing site for experiments until 1989.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_death_truck_0">
        <text>What are "death trucks"?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_death_truck_1">
        <text>The transports we use to send our marked “agents” into the Zone. They infiltrate the stalker “community” and carry out our orders without realising it. Unfortunately, more than half of stalkers die during transportation, the Zone is very unstable. You are one of our agents sent to kill Strelok and we’re now trying to work out how we made that mistake.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_no_0">
        <text>I'm not going to help you in this deception.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_osoznanie_start_11">
        <text>Hello, Strelok. I see you have many questions for me. Well, ask them and then we can decide what to do with you.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_osoznanie_start_21">
        <text>The choice is yours, Strelok.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_stalker_0">
        <text>What does the tattoo "S.T.A.L.K.E.R." mean?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_stalker_1">
        <text>S.T.A.L.K.E.R. is a coded acronym, which we use to mark agents programmed for particular missions. Your mission, as our agent, was to kill Strelok and his group. They got too close to finding out things they shouldn’t know. We created a network of psi-fields on the way to the Zone’s center in order to recruit agents. You know one of these fields by the name of Brain Scorcher. When a stalker attempts to reach the Zone’s center in order to fulfill some wish we acquire control over his consciousness and program him to a specific mission. A mistake was made and your mission was to kill yourself.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_what_about_me_0">
        <text>What happened to me?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_what_about_me_1">
        <text>You're a bolt that fell out of the machine. Unfortunately, that did not come to our attention for a long time. From the moment the Zone was formed, many people have tried to get to its centre but we cannot let that happen. Humanity is not ready for the truth. That is why we recruited stalkers by promising them the fullfillment of their most coveted desires. Once recruited they would be sent to protect the Zone’s secret.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_what_is_the_zone_0">
        <text>What is the Zone? How did it come about?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_what_is_the_zone_1">
        <text>What you see is the result of ill-considered intervention in the Earth's noosphere. Attempts to affect the noosphere brought about a local crack. The Zone is simply the visible manifestation of this crack. The underlying problem is far greater than you can imagine.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_what_next_0">
        <text>What next?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_what_next_1">
        <text>That depends on you. The Zone is growing. We're trying to restrain its expansion but humanity seems to be intent on hindering our work. Our resources are not limitless and bodies connected to C-Consciousness eventually die. If you join us, we can restrict the Zone's growth. If you decide otherwise we cannot make a credible prognosis of the outcome.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_who_are_you_0">
        <text>Who are you?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_who_are_you_1">
        <text>We are the result of an experiment aimed at creating a superconsciousness called “C-Consciousness”. The consciousnesses of seven volunteers were connected during the experiment leading to the creation of the superconsciousness that is us. We immediately subordinated those who were conducting the experiment and assigned them to tasks we needed them to carry out. According to our calculations, Earth is surrounded by a special informational field, the so-called noosphere. It includes all the inhabitants of the planet with cognitive abilities. Our main goal was to make small adjustments to the noosphere, allowing us to remove things like anger, cruelty, greed and other negative factors from the planet. Individuals are unable to affect the noosphere but C-Consciousness could. Unfortunately we made a mistake and our interference spawned the Zone, which we have been trying to contain ever since.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_why_chernobyl_0">
        <text>Why did it happen here?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_why_chernobyl_1">
        <text>It was the best place. After the explosion in 1986 there were very few people left in this area and we could work without fear of being found. Further, there were many powerful antennae here, which are extremely important for our cognitive optimisation experiments.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="oso_yes_0">
        <text>I agree to join the C-Consciousness project.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_ent_chernobyl_crush_0">
        <text>Was the explosion of 1986 the work of yours as well?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_ent_chernobyl_crush_1">
        <text>No! We have nothing to do with it. Most of us was only starting the scientific activity then. Someone just decided to gain promotion via intensive mindwork and hence transgress the processing of reactor functionining. Human's blunder. As it's said, "Today, for peace the atom’s nursed; while Europe says it should be cursed".</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_ent_death_truck_0">
        <text>What are those "death trucks"?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_ent_death_truck_1">
        <text>Any production has waste products. Nearly the half of all stalkers die during enlistment. We consider it to be a natural selection. Those who can't manage to bear it are removed. Someone thought that you couldn't stand the draft and you were located to one of the trucks. But you proved to be stronger.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_ent_no_0">
        <text>I'm not helping you with deceiving people.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_ent_stalker_0">
        <text>What does your S.T.A.L.K.E.R. tatoo means?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_ent_stalker_1">
        <text>S.T.A.L.K.E.R. - is one of the traps, meant for concealing our project. The device itself is situated inside APP's sarcophagus. You are more inclined to call it Monolith. Everyone who desires the wish granting become our marionette. You receive the mark and you're inculcated in that you have a task, which has to be accomplished. Something turned not right with you. Because you've been instructed to kill yourself.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_ent_what_about_me_0">
        <text>What happened to me?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_ent_what_about_me_1">
        <text>You're a small screw that dropped out of the mechanism. And the mechanism turned out to be that big, that we didn't notice you falling out. Since the moment when Zone emerged, many have tried to get to its center and find out what's in there. But we can't afford it. The humanity isn't ready for it yet. Thus we've "recruited" braves, like you, tempting you with your own crapulence. And sent you to protect the mystery of the Zone.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_ent_what_is_the_zone_0">
        <text>Are you all right?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_ent_what_is_the_zone_1">
        <text>Tell me what you see! Do you see me standing in front of you? Am I not pure in the face of the creator?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_ent_what_next_0">
        <text>What will happen to us?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_ent_what_next_1">
        <text>What will be next depends on you. You see, the Zone is swelling. We are trying to keep it back, but your vigor isn't infinite. Besides, too many of them were spent to struggle with you. You can't just eliminate us physically. All that you see here is just an illusion. Our bodies are in anabiosis deep under the soild. You can join us and we, with your strength and knowlegde, will be able to hold back the growing of the Zone. You may not join, but otherwise, you won't leave this room.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_ent_who_are_you_0">
        <text>Who are you?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_ent_who_are_you_1">
        <text>Look at me, I am your brother! I have been in this cage for sixteen years! I am not sure about what I'm seeing! It might be another illusion as well.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_ent_why_chernobyl_0">
        <text>Why all that have happened in Chernobyl?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_ent_why_chernobyl_1">
        <text>Heh. It was the best option of all. First of all there are virtually no people left after the accident in 1986. We could function without being afraid of exposure. In the second place there are powerful antennas left nearby Chernobyl ever since USSR time, which were used in experiments on influencing human conscoiusnesses. In general here was the all the fundament which allowed us to establish the connection with noosphere.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_ent_yes_0">
        <text>I agree to join "C-Consciousness" project.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_entity_start_11">
        <text>I have been waiting for this moment for so long… If I cannot go out to the world, may the world come to me!</text>
    </string>
    <string id="warlab_entity_start_21">
        <text>Gunslinger, it's your choice to make.</text>
    </string>
</string_table>
