<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
<string id="bad_psy_helmet_desc">
		<text>Prototype developed by scientists to protect people from psi-emissions. Needs adjusting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bad_psy_helmet_name">
		<text>Uncalibrated psi-helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="good_psy_helmet_desc">
		<text>Prototype developed by scientists to protect people from psi-emissions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="good_psy_helmet_name">
		<text>Psi-helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_key_short_desc">
		<text>Doctor's key to a secret stash in Pripyat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_key_name">
		<text>Doctor's key</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_key_desc">
		<text>A key with "Hotel Polissya - Room 26" engraved on side.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_docs_hiden_pri_desc">
		<text>Worn manuscript in leather binding. Written by Strelok himself. \nJudging by the headings alone, it might explain some of the Zone's secrets.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_pda_name">
		<text>Doctor's notes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_pda_desc">
		<text>"Just some notes about old men's conspiration theories". \nThere are rumours that the Agroprom Institute was used as a front for an unofficial lab in the years preceding the 2006 year accident. This lab hosted a number of very unusual experiments. The traders have dug up a lot of information about these laboratories. I met with the Barkeep, he says he sent Duty scouts to get into the underground vaults of Dark Valley, called X-18, but they disappeared. There are another rumours regarding a "Psi-Brain" mechanism. The whole neigborhood in Yantar is under the influence of that piece of trash - it zombified everyone who came within range. There is another mechanism in Red Forest radar underground, called Lab X-10, and that's what is likely to be the Brain Scorcher. There is evidence to suggest that the presence of the Brain Scorcher intentionally blocks the road to the North, but no one knows exactly what it is. The Barkeep believes that the Brain Scorcher is man-made, and these mechanisms are not always operating at full strength. He thinks there are periods when their power is lowered to cool down the apparatus. It's time to visit all the underground laboratories in the Zone and find out what kind of secrets they are hiding. Too bad, that I'm too old for this shit. I wish Strelok would be still around, but damn, he disappeared years ago.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_docs_hiden_pri_name">
		<text>Strelok's manuscript</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_decoder_desc">
		<text>A powerful electronic lockpick. Strangely enough, it does not seem to be an all-purpose thieves' instrument. Rather, it seems to have been created with a specific electronic lock in mind and can't be used to override anything else.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_decoder_name">
		<text>Decoder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_decoder_docs_conclusion_txt">
		<text>The manuscript contains a short report on how Fang and Strelok infiltrated a hidden laboratory and their journey there. It makes mention of large Monolith presence in and around the Chernobyl NPP. More specifically under the concrete sarcophagus, also suggesting it may be their base of operations but with the intent to hide something. Reading further it states that they discovered laboratory hidden further in the north under the generators, however they were unable to gain access at the time of writing as they required the use of a decoder.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_quest_case_02_desc">
		<text>A fireproof briefcase with documents.\nInvestigation report.\n For official use only.\n To SBU Colonel V.M. Kruchelnikov, head of project "TRUTH".\n From Captain D.F. Maksimenko, \ncommander of "Search-2" group.\n\n Memo.\n Our group consisting of 3 investigators and a squad of SBU Special Forces conducted searched at Agroprom, the former Research Institute for agriculture on radiation-affected soil, from 12.05.2012 to 25.05.2012. Most of the equipment and documentation was missing however the few things we were able to find allow us to come to the following conclusion: over the period from 2005 to 2008, the Institute did not conduct any research in its official fields of study. All the results of its "work" sent to the Ministry of Agriculture were falsified. Simultaneously, the Institute's management, specifically Petr Danilovich Strizh, continued to receive state financing, equipment and consumables and transferred them to a laboratory designated X18 using forged consignment notes, which provided cover for the operation by indicating that the materials were being transferred to an auxiliary facility for experiments. X18 appears to be a code name adopted by the group of people implicated in this affair, since our database contains no mention of this laboratory. Judging by the analysis of the documents we found, this laboratory is located within an hour's drive from the Institute. It is likely to be a clandestine facility so I would request the involvement of our analytical department. The lab's field of research is not clear and available documents contain no helpful information in this regard but do make references to the infamous professor Chubko and also mention some "Group". It is my firm belief that we have come to the end of the line and the analytical department will now have plenty of work to do.\n\n Attached is an archived file containing consignment notes for consumable materials and equipment transferred to some auxiliary facility and an extract from correspondence between Strizh and Chubko.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_quest_case_02_name">
		<text>Military documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x18_name">
		<text>Documents from Lab X18</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x18_desc">
		<text>A thick pile of scientific documents.\nTerms, formulas, and a number of diagrams.\nThe report details the study of biological samples sent from lab X18. The samples were subjected to informational field effects of varying intensities. The report meticulously describes the mutation of living beings following exposure to emissions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x16_desc">
		<text>Plastic document file.\nYou'd need a degree in biology to understand a word of what it says.\nThe documents refer to one of the side discoveries of the research, specifically the discovery that living creatures are able to generate directed psy-emissions. A biological field emitter, essentially a giant brain, was grown as part of the research conducted in lab X16.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x16_name">
		<text>Documents from Lab X16</text>
	</string>
		<string id="item_doc_x10_desc">
		<text>The documents describe the technical characteristics of the antenna and how they deviate from their planned values. There is a note on the reverse side which indicates that these documents were prepared in lab X10.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x10_name">
		<text>Rainbow emitter - main technical characteristics</text>
	</string>
		<string id="item_doc_x8_desc">
		<text>The document refers to the transfer of the research team and all materials to another laboratory called War Lab, which will be used to research matters relating to the influence of the noosphere. To enter the lab, use the date of the accident for code. The research team comprises: N.A. Lebedev, E.F. Kalancha and V.I. Suslov.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x8_name">
		<text>Order of Transfer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_jup_ug_desc">
		<text>The notebook contains a detailed description of an experiment assessing a psy-field's effect on an object in another hemisphere. A group of scientists in the Caribbean received the signal, but it was distorted. The signal was altered in a strange way, as though corrected by someone. A possible explanation is that the noosphere theory is correct and the changes were made by the noosphere.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_jup_ug_name">
		<text>A notebook with a description of an experiment</text>
	</string>
		<string id="item_doc_mon_con_name">
		<text>Documents concerning Super Gauss</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_mon_con_name_desc">
		<text>Documents which describe the operating mechanism and main technical characteristics of a more advanced electromagnetic device.\nThere is a note inside the documents which reads: "Documents must be returned to X8, the central laboratory. I will be busy, so deliver them yourself.\nN. Lebedev"</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
