<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
<string id="bad_psy_helmet_desc">
		<text>Prototype developed by scientists to protect people from psi-emissions. Needs adjusting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bad_psy_helmet_name">
		<text>Uncalibrated psi-helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="good_psy_helmet_desc">
		<text>Prototype developed by scientists to protect people from psi-emissions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="good_psy_helmet_name">
		<text>Psi-helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_key_short_desc">
		<text>Doctor's key to a secret stash in Pripyat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_key_name">
		<text>Doctor's key</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_key_desc">
		<text>A key with "Hotel Polissya - Room 26" engraved on side.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_docs_hiden_pri_desc">
		<text>Worn manuscript in leather binding. Written by Strelok himself. Judging by the headings alone, it might explain some of the Zone's secrets.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_docs_hiden_pri_name">
		<text>Strelok's manuscript</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_decoder_desc">
		<text>A powerful electronic lockpick. Strangely enough, it does not seem to be an all-purpose thieves' instrument. Rather, it seems to have been created with a specific electronic lock in mind and can't be used to override anything else.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_decoder_name">
		<text>Decoder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_decoder_docs_conclusion_txt">
		<text>The manuscript contains a short report on how Fang and Strelok infiltrated a hidden laboratory and their journey there. It makes mention of large Monolith presence in and around the Chernobyl NPP. More specifically under the concrete sarcophagus, also suggesting it may be their base of operations but with the intent to hide something. Reading further it states that they discovered laboratory hidden further in the north under the generators, however they were unable to gain access at the time of writing as they required the use of a decoder.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
