<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
<string id="bad_psy_helmet_desc">
		<text>Prototype developed by scientists to protect people from psi-emissions. Needs adjusting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bad_psy_helmet_name">
		<text>Uncalibrated psi-helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="good_psy_helmet_desc">
		<text>Prototype developed by scientists to protect people from psi-emissions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="good_psy_helmet_name">
		<text>Psi-helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_key_short_desc">
		<text>Doctor's key to a secret stash in Pripyat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_key_name">
		<text>Doctor's key</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_key_desc">
		<text>A key with "Hotel Polissya - Room 26" epigraph</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_docs_hiden_pri_desc">
		<text>Worn manuscript in leather binding. Written by Strelok himself. Judging by the headings alone, it might explain some of the Zone's secrets.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_docs_hiden_pri_name">
		<text>Documents from the secret stash in Pripyat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_decoder_desc">
		<text>Powerful electronic lockpick. Strangely enough, it does not seem to be an all-purpose thieves' instrument. Rather, it seems to have been created with a specific electronic lock in mind and can't be used to override anything else.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_decoder_name">
		<text>Decoder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_decoder_docs_conclusion_txt">
		<text>The document contains a short report on how Fang and Strelok infiltrated the laboratory under the Generators and found a suspicious-looking door. Fang said that he'd put together a decoder for the electronic lock for their next visit. After that they had to run for their lives. There were hordes of Monolith patrols there. Well. The decoder was in the stash too and directions for finding the door. It seems that approaching the Monolith is extremely dangerous - last time they avoided going under the sarcophagus above the destroyed reactor and it seems that's where the Monolith is. The Wish Granter is just an illusion, manufactured by unknown forces in a lab next to the Generators, to protect their secret. After a 'wish' has been granted, the Zone expands 5 km. The wish itself is an illusion or a violent trick.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
