<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_faction_stalker">
		<text>Loner</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_stalker_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]Nomadic groups of stalkers who have united because of the aggressions against them from the Military and Bandits. They can be found anywhere in the Zone, but have main bases in the Cordon for beginners and at the Skadovsk at Zaton, for more advanced stalkers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_bandit">
		<text>Bandit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_bandit_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]A loose collection of criminals and brigands. They are usually hostile to Loners and the other factions. They hold several unorganized bases and camps throughout the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_dolg">
		<text>Duty</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_dolg_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]A para-military group trying to "kill" the Zone and stop it from spreading. They consider the Zone to be alive and evil. Duty and Freedom are at war with each other, but both are based in the Yanov train station, which is a mutual cease-fire zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_freedom">
		<text>Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_freedom_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]A faction of stalkers trying to make the Zone available for everyone, so that mankind can understand this wonder. They believe that the Zone is a gift to mankind which should be free to everyone and no one should tell them otherwise. They are based in Yanov, together with Duty.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_army">
		<text>Military</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_army_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]The armed forces of Ukraine, dispatched to the center of the Zone with the task of trying to learn more about the Chernobyl Nuclear Power Plant, and ultimately to control the area. They are constantly harassed by the Monolith faction.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_ecolog">
		<text>Ecologist</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_ecolog_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]Stationed in a mobile lab in Jupiter and another one in Yantar, they are scientists who have come to investigate and study the Zone, learn more about anomalies, artifacts and mutants, and develop experimental equipment associated with the Zone. They also believe that the Zone is a gift to mankind; however, unlike Freedom they don't believe in violence to achieve their goals. Neutral to all. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_killer">
		<text>Mercenary</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_killer_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]Hired by various unnamed contractors, they will do any job for the right sum of money. Their primary objectives are to secure and investigate the secret labs of the Zone and whatever their contractors ask them.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_monolith">
		<text>Monolith</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_monolith_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]A faction that has fanatically religious interests in the Zone. They were once regular stalkers, until they were brain-washed by the C-Consciousness and are now the unquestioning foot soldiers of the C-Con. Hostile to all and hated equally.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_csky">
		<text>Clear Sky</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_csky_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]A scientific faction trying to understand the zone and learn about it. Clear Sky is the oldest known Faction in the Zone. Their base of operations is on the south-western section of the swamps west of the Cordon. They were almost totally wiped out from the Zone after their assault on the CNPP but are still popular to stalkers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_back">
		<text>Back</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_submit">
		<text>Start</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_cap_character_name">
		<text>Name:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_cap_faction">
		<text>Faction:</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
