<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_faction_stalker">
		<text>Loner</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_stalker_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]Often referred to as "free stalkers", loners are unaligned with any major faction that operates within the Zone. Despite often being harassed by Bandits and Military alike, they have managed to establish small outposts of relative tranquility. Such places include a small abandoned village in the Cordon and the Skadovsk in Zaton.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_bandit">
		<text>Bandit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_bandit_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]Bandits are members of the criminal underworld who came to the Zone for different reasons; to make money by selling artifacts, hide from the law or to trade in weapons. Whilst they have no central leadership, they have managed to establish a headquarters out of an abandoned factory in the north of the Dark Valley.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_dolg">
		<text>Duty</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_dolg_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]Duty is a paramilitary clan of stalkers operating in the Zone with members living according to a certain code. Along with Freedom, they are also one of the most powerful stalker clans in the Zone, which in addition to competing ideologies has kept them in a state of conflict. They occupy a stronghold not too far from the 100 Rads Bar.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_freedom">
		<text>Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_freedom_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]Freedom is paramilitary a clan of stalkers who fight for free access to the Zone, seeing it as a scientific marvel, which puts them at odds with Duty who seek the opposite. Their headquarters is currently situated in abandoned Army Warehouses, which under constant threat from Duty in the south, Monolith in the north and Mercenaries in the west.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_army">
		<text>Military</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_army_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]The Ukrainian government, through its Ministry of Internal Affairs, maintains the Zone's perimeter with internal troops from the State Security Service. They also occupy numerous outposts through the Zone, with more notable ones in the Cordon, Darkscape, the Swamps and the Agroprom Research Institute.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_ecolog">
		<text>Ecologist</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_ecolog_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]The Ecologists are a government-funded group focused on researching the Zone in order to properly harness its potential for the good of mankind. Their base of operations is a sturdy bunker at Lake Yantar, however in recent years they have expanded their operations further afield and have established a second base not far from Yanov station.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_killer">
		<text>Mercenary</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_killer_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]The Mercenary faction is a group of private military contractors operating within the Zone, though their clients are kept highly secret. Their base of operations currently resides in the Dead City, with other small outposts scattered throughout the Zone. One notable example being the waste processing plant in Zaton.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_monolith">
		<text>Monolith</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_monolith_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]The Monolith stalker clan is a xenophobic religious cult, hostile to all but their own, with an extremely strong presence in areas of significant importance in the Zone, such as Pripyat, Radar, Chernobyl NPP and Generators. A typical Monolithian is a former stalker brainwashed by one of the psychic emitters throughout the Zone into serving the will of the C-Consciousness, unflinchingly loyal and ready to sacrifice himself at a moment's notice.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_csky">
		<text>Clear Sky</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_csky_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]Clear Sky is an independent scientific and military organization focused on understanding the Zone. Almost completely collapsing several years ago after a disastrous assault on Chernobyl NPP, a handful of the few surviving members have since gradually restored the faction to its original stature. Like before, their headquarters and area of operations are located in the Swamps.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_back">
		<text>Back</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_submit">
		<text>Start</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_cap_character_name">
		<text>Name:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_cap_faction">
		<text>Faction:</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
