<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_faction_stalker">
		<text>Loner</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_stalker_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]Loners, or free stalkers, are unaligned with any of the factions that operate within the Zone.\n \nDespite being frequently harassed by roaming mutants, bandits and the military, small groups have managed to establish strong trading outposts throughout the Zone.\n \nNotable examples include Rookie Village in the Cordon and aboard the Skadovsk in Zaton.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_bandit">
		<text>Bandit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_bandit_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]Bandits are members of the criminal underworld who came to the Zone for different reasons; to make money by selling artefacts, to hide from the law or even to trade in weapons.\n \nDespite having no central leadership or command structure, they have managed to establish a base of operations within an abandoned factory in the north of the Dark Valley.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_dolg">
		<text>Duty</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_dolg_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]Duty is a paramilitary faction at odds with everyone seeking to exploit the Zone and, as Duty sees it, spread its corruption.\n \nThey have long been in fierce conflict with Freedom due to their conflicting ideals.\n \nThey occupy a stronghold located east of the Wild Territory, not far from the 100 Rads bar.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_freedom">
		<text>Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_freedom_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]Freedom are anarchists and daredevils who declare themselves to be fighting for free access to the Zone and consequently find themselves in constant conflict with Duty.\n \nTheir headquarters are located at the Army Warehouses but they can also be found elsewhere in the Zone at their smaller outposts.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_army">
		<text>Military</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_army_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]The Ukrainian government, through its Ministry of Internal Affairs, maintains the Zone's perimeter with internal troops from the State Security Service.\n \nThey also occupy numerous forward bases within the Zone, most notably at the Agroprom Research Institute and at a checkpoint located towards the south of the Cordon.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_ecolog">
		<text>Ecologist</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_ecolog_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]The Ecologists are a government-funded body researching the Zone in order to properly harness its potential for the good of mankind.\n \nThey operate from two near-identical bunkers, one located in Yantar, south of the factory complex, and another further afield in Jupiter.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_killer">
		<text>Mercenary</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_killer_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]Mercenaries are experienced fighters from all walks of life who offer their services as hired soldiers, it is unknown who their clients are or why they have interests in the Zone.\n \nTheir headquarters can be located within the Dead City with several other smaller outposts scattered throughout the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_monolith">
		<text>Monolith</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_monolith_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]Monolith are a fanatical religious cult hostile to all but their own.\n \nDespite the destruction of the C-Conciousness and the subsequent fallout, they have since re-emerged as a resurgent force, retaking Pripyat, Chernobyl NPP, Generators and Radar.\n \nSince re-enabling the Brain Scorcher they have found no difficulty in securing their advances.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_csky">
		<text>Clear Sky</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_csky_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]Clear Sky is an independent scientific and military organisation focused on researching and understanding the Zone.\n \nFacing almost complete collapse after a failed and costly assault on Chernobyl NPP, a handful of the few remaining survivors managed to rebuild the faction to its former stature.\n \nTheir isolated headquarters and most of their operations are located in the Swamps.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_back">
		<text>Back</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_submit">
		<text>Start</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_rand">
		<text>Randomize</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_cap_character_name">
		<text>Name:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_cap_faction">
		<text>Faction:</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
