<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<!--      esc_m_trader_task_*	 -->
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_1_name">
		<text>Contract killer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_1_text">
		<text>Sidrovich contracted you to run a hit. Find and eliminate the target then return to Sidrovich for payment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_1_about">
		<text>I have a list of outstanding bounties and stalkers that need taken care of. The worst kind of scum and villainy usually end up on this list... for various reasons. The Zone needs it's trash taken out from time to time. What do you say, stalker, will you be my "hired gun?"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_2_name">
		<text>Eliminate bandits at the Car Park</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_2_text">
		<text>Stage an assault on the Car Park and eliminate the bandits that occupy the location.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_2_about">
		<text>Bandits have taken up base in the old Car Park. These assholes mug or kill anyone who use the roads leading in and out of the camp. It is disrupting local activities for my clients and the stalkers who take refuge in camp. It's hurting business! I need you to "take care" of them. If you want, talk to Fanatic, he may be able to offer you assistance.</text>
	</string>
	<!--     esc_2_12_stalker_wolf	 -->
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_1_name">
		<text>Eliminate the mutant threat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_1_text">
		<text>Wolf asked you to purge an area of all mutant threat in order to ensure the safety of rookie village; as well as the stalkers who pass through Cordon. Reach the location and eliminate all mutants around the area. Return to Wolf for payment after you job is complete.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_1_about">
		<text>Stalker, I need someone to who is a bit more experienced than the rookies for a task. Cordon is becoming a very dangerous place with all this rampant mutant breeding going on. I need you to hunt around an area that I will mark on your PDA. The job is to kill any mutants you see. If you do this for me, it will earn you some cash. So will you?</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
